Narrator: 1
a
Speaker 1: Do you think Sundays are usually boring?
Narrator: b
Speaker 2: Are you bored with your job or studies?
Narrator: 2
a
Speaker 1: What kind of weather makes you feel depressed?
Narrator: b
Speaker 2: Do you think the news is always depressing?
Narrator: 3
a
Speaker 1: What activities do you find relaxing?
Narrator: b
Speaker 2: Do you usually feel relaxed at the end of the weekend?
Narrator: 4
a
Speaker 1: Have you read any interesting articles or books recently?
Narrator: b
Speaker 2: What sports are you interested in?
Narrator: 5
a
Speaker 1: Are you excited about your next holiday?
Narrator: b
Speaker 2: Are you doing anything exciting next weekend?
Narrator: 6
a
Speaker 1: What were you frightened of when you were a child?
Narrator: b
Speaker 2: Do you find horror films frightening?